ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Q: Corning Glass
  - UAW Conventions, 1998-1999 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Corning AFGWU - IIS Project Shared Visions, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    Overhead Papers; Corning Booklet
  - Corning Local PEL (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Corning News Clippings (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Corning Pressware (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Corning Sullivan Park (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Corning Erwin (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Corning Partnership Education, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Corning General Information (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Corning History (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Focus on the Future Timesheets (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Focus on the Future Materials (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - AFGWU History (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Sample Ballots (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Team Failure (Box 35, Folder 31)